<?xml version="1.0"?>
<boilerplate xmlns="https://niap-ccevs.org/cc/v1">
  <cc-terms>
    <term full="Assurance">Grounds for confidence that a TOE meets the SFRs <citeCC/>.</term>
    <term full="Base Protection Profile" abbr="Base-PP">Protection Profile used as a basis to build a PP-Configuration.</term>
    <term full="Common Criteria" abbr="CC">Common Criteria for Information Technology Security Evaluation (International Standard ISO/IEC 15408).</term>
    <term full="Common Criteria Testing Laboratory">
      Within the context of the Common Criteria Evaluation and Validation Scheme (CCEVS), an IT security evaluation facility, accredited by the National Voluntary Laboratory Accreditation Program (NVLAP) and approved by the NIAP Validation Body to conduct Common Criteria-based evaluations.
    </term>
    <term full="Common Evaluation Methodology" abbr="CEM">Common Evaluation Methodology for Information Technology Security Evaluation.</term>
    <term full="Distributed TOE">A TOE composed of multiple components operating as a logical whole.</term>
    <term full="Operational Environment" abbr="OE">Hardware and software that are outside the TOE boundary that support the TOE functionality and security policy.</term>
    <term full="Protection Profile" abbr="PP">An implementation-independent set of security requirements for a category of products.</term>
    <term full="Protection Profile Configuration" abbr="PP-Configuration">A comprehensive set of security requirements for a product type that consists of at least one Base-PP and at least one PP-Module.</term>
    <term full="Protection Profile Module" abbr="PP-Module">An implementation-independent statement of security needs for a TOE type complementary to one or more Base Protection Profiles.</term>
    <term full="Security Functional Requirement" abbr="SFR">A requirement for security enforcement by the TOE.</term>
    <term full="Security Assurance Requirement" abbr="SAR">A requirement to assure the security of the TOE.</term>
    <term full="Security Target" abbr="ST">A set of implementation-dependent security requirements for a specific product.</term>
    <term full="Target of Evaluation" abbr="TOE">The product under evaluation. </term>
    <term full="TOE Security Functionality" abbr="TSF">The security functionality of the product under evaluation.</term>
    <term full="TOE Summary Specification" abbr="TSS">A description of how a TOE satisfies the SFRs in an ST.</term>
  </cc-terms>

  <!-- ############## -->
   <empty title='Security Requirements'>
     This chapter describes the security requirements which have to be fulfilled by the product under evaluation.
     Those requirements comprise functional components from Part 2 and assurance components from Part 3 of <citeCC/>.
     The following conventions are used for the completion of operations:
     <ul xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
       <li>
         <b>Refinement</b> operation (denoted by <b>bold text</b> or <strike>strikethrough
         text</strike>): is used to add details to a requirement (including replacing an assignment
         with a more restrictive selection) or to remove part of the requirement that is made irrelevant
         through the completion of another operation, and thus further restricts a requirement.
         </li>
       <li>
         <b>Selection</b> (denoted by <i>italicized text</i>): is used to select one or more options
         provided by the [CC] in stating a requirement.</li>
       <li>
         <b>Assignment</b> operation (denoted by <span class="assignable-content">italicized text</span>): is used to assign a
         specific value to an unspecified parameter, such as the length of a password. Showing the
         value in square brackets indicates assignment.</li>
       <li>
         <b>Iteration</b> operation: is indicated by appending the SFR name with a slash and unique identifier
            suggesting the purpose of the operation, e.g. "/EXAMPLE1."
       </li>
     </ul>
   </empty>

   <empty id="a-group">
      <a-stuff type="D">Developer action</a-stuff>
      <a-stuff type="C">Content and presentation</a-stuff>
      <a-stuff type="E">Evaluator action</a-stuff>
   </empty>

   <empty id="DCE">
     <D/><C/><E/>
   </empty>
   
   <empty id="cc-ref-docs">
	  <doc num="1" name="Introduction and General Model"/>
   	  <doc num="2" name="Security Functional Components"/>
   	  <doc num="3" name="Security Assurance Components"/>
   </empty>

   <empty id="req-types">
       <mt tp='optional'   nice='Strictly Optional'/>
       <mt tp='objective'  nice='Objective'/>
       <mt tp='feat-based' nice='Implementation-based'/>
       <mt tp='sel-based'  nice='Selection-based'/>
   </empty>



   
</boilerplate>
